Jane Got a Gun is a western, action, drama film directed by Gavin O'Connor.
After her outlaw husband returns home shot with eight bullets and barely alive, Jane reluctantly reaches out to an ex-lover who she hasn't seen in
over ten years to help her defend her farm when the time comes that her husband's gang eventually tracks him down to finish the job.
Jane Hammond, played by Natalie Portman.
Dan Frost, played by Joel Edgerton.
John Bishop, played by Ewan McGregor.
Bill Hammond, played by Noah Emmerich.
Vic Owen, played by Boyd Holbrook.
Fitchum, played by Rodrigo Santoro.
Jane Got a Gun is a 2015 American Western film directed by Gavin O'Connor and
written by Brian Duffield, Joel Edgerton, and Anthony Tambakis.
The film stars Natalie Portman, Joel Edgerton, Noah Emmerich,
Rodrigo Santoro, Boyd Holbrook and Ewan McGregor.
After a long period of production issues since 2012, involving director and
casting changes, principal photography began on March 21, 2013.
The film was released on January 29, 2016.
The film was shown on October 12, 2017 at the 7th Almería Western Film Festival.
The tone is emotional.